(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Tracy had to take a vocabulary quiz.
She needed her pen.
She looked inside her bag, but the pen
wasn't in there.
It was always there.
She just used it yesterday.
She decided to let it go.
She also needed a piece of paper.
She looked inside her bag.
There was no paper.
Did she leave everything at home?
Was she becoming forgetful?
Was someone stealing from her?
She borrowed paper from a friend.
She also needed an eraser.
She looked inside her bag.
No eraser.
She screamed, oh my god!
Her classmates stared at her.
She apologized.
Her classmate then pointed at the bottom of
her bag.
There was a huge hole.